Food Safety问题爬取结果：

I’m cooking hotdogs and bringing them to a boil in some beans. Is this safe? 5wks 4days
Pregnant how to deal with alcoholic husband ?
8 weeks pregnant and ate ceviche as I was unaware it had raw fish. I felt totally fine after eating it, but worried it might affect my little raspberry. Should I be worried?
Sharp pains in the stomach and lower back? 33 weeks
Why are you supposed to cut caffeine completely during the last few weeks of pregnancy?
Is it bad to eat anything spicy during the 1st trimester?
My wife just called me weeping because she found out the prenatal vitamins that an old doctor prescribed have 4000mg of Vitamin A.
Armaforce (containing Andrographis) safe?
Does anyone have any tips for food prep for work lunches during the week?
Nutritional yeast during  pregnancy?
How serious is the Listeria problem in lunch meats these days?
is rosemary safe to eat while pregnant?
Is there a good brand of granola bars or specific “pregnancy bars” I can buy to have a healthy snack between meals?
My mom got me groceries but left them in her car for 4 hrs (didn't even tell me had to look at the receipt) are they all bad now? Lots of cheese and cream cheese what would you do
Does my baby get everything it needs from prenatal vitamins?
Has anyone used the 310 shake products while pregnant? My first appt with my Dr isn’t until Nov 8 and i’d like to know. My intention is to use the shakes as a snack between meals.
Drinking aloe Vera juice in 3rd trimester?
Is garlic salt or powder, or any kind of garlic ok during pregnancy? I've read garlic is a blood thinner and i should be careful.
Unbeknownst to me, I’ve been indulging in an unpasteurized orange juice for the past few weeks. I’m 12 weeks now. Have I caused any harm to the baby?
Is eating Carvel ice cream cake safe ?
Has anyone had food poisoning while pregnant?
is it okay to drink the organic pregnancy tea , herbal tea ?
Ice Dragon Breath??
Chewing gum with sugar alcohol and aspartame ok?
Is anyone else feeling frustrated over people passing judgement on food choices?
How to beat the flu?
Fiber One bars being the common bars to avoid, did anybody know about Luna bars having the chicory ingredient? I didn’t know and I’m upset with myself!
Can you eat muscadine grapes?
Is Boost drink healthy to drink while preggo?
Shredded mozzarella cheese safe to eat on a salad from a restaurant?
I am 20 weeks pregnant and I cnt stay away from spicy food and cold water. Could it be bad to my baby?
Can I drink coconut water during pregnancy?

Food poisoning?
I’m 4 weeks pregnant and nursing my 10 month old, I don’t want to ween him before the new baby arrives, he will only just be 18 months old in December. Tips?
What groceries to buy?
Is Jamba Juice safe?
First bout nausea at 16 weeks 3 days?
What can you eat while pregnant during the holidays I’m only 8weeks this week and I always look forward to the holiday food is there anything I shouldn’t eat?
Shin ramyun?
How many grams/mgs of protein do you need whilst in the first trimester?
I just had two glasses of tonic water and lemon and then looked up tonic water online and now am concerned that drinking tonic water might be unsafe. What's the word on this??
Is prosciutto safe to eat while pregnant?
Diet with gestational diabetes.?
Almost 9 weeks & had bad food poisining, but they didn't test to see which bacteria caused it. Can Listeria (for eg) cause birth defects this early on? Or is the risk miscarriage?
Anyone not eat healthy and everything turned out okay?
Is it bad to eat really spicy food while pregnant??
What’s for Dinner?
Is protein powder alright to drink while pregnant ?
Is it okay to eat?
Recalled food?
Hot smoked turkey sandwich from a bbq restaurant, should I be worried?
What can you eat during the first trimester?
What can I do for indigestion/heartburn?
8 wks pregnant and ate medium done red meat (ate small portion)...I didn't realize I couldn't eat it until after (face palm). Should I be worried abt toxoplasmosis?
Is chewing ice bad during pregnancy?
Can i eat donner meat?
I drank some Gatorade today when I saw something floating in the bottom of the bottle and it looked to be mold?? I’m only 9 weeks and 3 days pregnant. What should I do??
Outback Steakhouse’s blue cheese chopped salad... the local restaurant can’t tell me if the cheese is pasteurized. I’m diabetic so my diet is already so limited. Is it safe?
Rapid weight gain at 18 weeks??
Has anyone used Marine Phytoplankton or Oceans Alive while pregnant? Is it safe?
I'm 29 weeks pregnant and I'm barely eating or drinking. I want to, but the food doesn't stay down! Also folic acid makes me feel nauseous so I've stopped taking it. What can I do?
Is twinings lemon ginger tea safe to drink for nasea in early pregnancy? Reading mixed answers.
Is it safe/doable to go on a keto or paleo diet while pregnant?
Is adkins greek yogurt bars safe during pregnancy?
Tilapia Florentine from ihop
Is it safe? I am 8 weeks pregnant and there's an ihop around the corner and I really want some but is it safe?
Can Feta cheese really hurt my baby?
Midwives Brew!? Did I do it right?
Can i eat marmite?
All I drink is water on a day to day basis, until recently when I do I gag and get nauseous after, what can I replace water with? Any suggestions
Top Ramen Oodles of Noodles in moderation? Yes or no? It's something I'm craving at 8 weeks now. Is it going to hurt my growing baby?
What are some good teas to drink while pregnant?
How often can you eat red meat?
Im 211 lb 5.8" and only 6 weeks pregnant....im 23 years old.... please tell me how can i lose weight safly? How much can i lose?
Are some sodas better than others when drank in moderation?
There is a pet dog (dachshund) and 8 feral cats that come and go anytime at in-laws’ place. I am not interested in pets but my in laws are. How do I manage?
I have painful gas cramps. Is it ok to take Beano?
Anyone else struggling with what the can and can’t eat?
Can I eat raw fish that was caught the same day?
Gas/bloating relief?
Ate at a quiche made with farm fresh eggs at restaurant and realized eggs were not pasteurized.  I assume since it wasn't soft cheese and quiche was fully set, there is no risk?

Help I have been consuming local honey and had no idea it was harmful! What should I do?
Bought traditional medicinals Pregnancy Tea, but I've heard conflicting info whether it's safe.  I think bc of the stinging nettle leaf.  Anyone drink it or heard the same?
Is anyone else completely paranoid about everything they eat because of listeria risk?
Can spicy food that gave me GI upset (diarrhea) make my in utero baby release meconium?
What was the last meal you ate, which helped get you through labor and delivery? & What snacks did you pack?
Is fluoride toothpaste bad for my baby?
Can pregnant women consume Stingray?
I weighed 125lbs (I am 5'2) when I found out I was having my baby. I am 7 months today and weigh in at 170. What do I do!? What can too much weight gain cause? Can this hurt baby?
Is milk thistle safe to take during pregnancy?
Is it safe to eat dried seaweed during pregnancy?
What is the best breast pump to use? Ftm,
Medela, Evenflo, or Lansinoh?
What kind of dairy can/should you eat and drink when pregnant?
Freaking out....just ate Costco Chinese chicken salad and I’m scared I just ate unsafe food for my little nugget. I’ll be 6 weeks tomorrow. Should I worry?
 I’m expecting my first baby in October and over the moon! I am a serious tea drinker- black tea in particular. Is it harmful to my baby to drink one cup a day?
I usually eat meat, and now the thought of it is repulsive. Is this normal? And what can I do to substitute for the protein?
Vomiting and diarrhea during third trimester. Should I be worried?
Any difference between consuming our precious 200mg caffeine allotment in No-Doze pill form versus coffee/pop?
23 weeks pregnant and diarrhea for over 24 hours. At what point should I worry that it is more serious such as salmonella or etc?
Can I eat rotisserie chicken?
My diet consists of a lot of vitamin A from natural sources.   I have a cup of spinach once a day, an egg, lots of leafy veg and red and yellow veg.  Is this harmful!?
Is it normal to eat a lot? I'm constantly hungry. My first pregnancy was a total opposite & I could hold anything down
Please help me with a diet chart beginning from the first meal to the last?
Have any of you used castor oil to kick start labor? Did it work?
Maternal PKU
What to do if you eat something unpasteurised? Should you contact your midwife?
I’m three months pregnant and everytime I reheat leftovers I end up throwing up (only when I eat reheated leftovers) anyone else?
Spinach and artichoke dip from the deli?
Well am been craving shrimp ceviche but am wondering if I cook the shrimp or use cooked shrimp will it be safe to eat
Is caffeine free coke okay to drink?
Is it safe to use psyllium husk during pregancy?
So I have a slight addiction to frozen cheesecake bites ( the “our finest chocolate cheesecake bites” to be exact! )  🤤  I’m pregnant & worried I can’t have them? Are they safe?
Is it safe for me to eat greek salad?
Is it safe for me to eat greek salad?
What kind  of grains can’t you eat on first trimester?
Is it bad that when I take my prenatal vitamin late in the day I can’t eat?
Is it safe to eat honey during pregnancy?
Is drinking cinnamon tea out of organic cinnamon sticks bad during pregnancy?
Sushi or Not To Sushi?
Is it ok to take BCAA’s during pregnancy? I’m used to having them every day at the gym. I use the xtendd brand.
Sucky feeling in stomach and no appetite. Is this normal?
Can I eat deli meat? I don't think I can go 9 months of packed lunches without turkey or ham.
Everysince i got pregnant ive been craving for chocolates im 32 weeks now and i am trying to control not to eat too much , isit safe for the baby?
Is eating barbaque harmful while pregnant if cooked to temperature?
Can I eat protein bars while pregnant? CLIF is the brand.
listeria
Why avoid (raw) sushi?
I Don’t Drink Milk, What Else Can I Do?
Is it safe to drink raw unfiltered apple cider vinegar?
Is it safe to drink prune juice?
Is it safe to drink prune juice?
What is a good diet plan for pregnant,  breastfeeding moms? I want to be sure to take on enough for both babies and myself.
I've always been underweight and unable to put on weight, no matter what I eat.  What do I do to gain weight during the pregnancy? Will
Hormones help to start gaining weight?
Caffeine free options?
Is it safe to eat salmon?
Is it ok to eat buffet food? Specifically fruit that’s been cut and is chilled like cantaloupe/honeydew/pineapple/etc? Is there risk for listeria?
Is ginger powder safe during pregnancy?
Is it ok for me to eat almonds?
Is it safe to take extra vitamins along with a prenatal? Such as a B-complex?
Is it safe to take extra vitamins along with a prenatal? Such as a B-complex?
What kinds of teas are Ok? I have a honey vanilla chamomile and a cinnamon Apple spice!
Does anyone know how many mg of caffeine is in a shot of espresso? I love to have my almond milk latte w two shots of espresso but don’t want to have any complications. 4 weeks in.
I'll be 24 weeks pregnant and we have an 18 day trip to Japan scheduled. I'm going to buy travel insurance just in case. Anything I should be worried about?? Nitrates and food?
13 Weeks and I have gained 25 pounds. For my first pregnancy I gained about 90 pounds and they were worried about me hurting baby, baby hurting me or baby be heavy when he came out
What are the most important things to avoid?
I am getting over the tummy “flu” and can tell I’m very dehydrated... does anyone know if Pedialite is safe to drink while pregnant?
Chinese food? Safe to eat or no?
Is beef jerky safe to eat during pregnancy?
Is beef jerky safe to eat during pregnancy?
Miso soup can pregnant woman have it im 15wks?
Is most blue cheese in restaurants pasteurized?
Any other moms to be predominantly or entirely plant based?
Is it ok and or better to eat Ezekiel bread / live grain bread?
I’m currently 15 weeks, and I’ve been feeling like shit cause my appetite. I get hungry, but when I see food, I don’t want to eat most of the time. I feel weak a lot. Any advice ?
Are there any spices you should avoid?
Preworkout and supplements prior to finding out I'm pregnant, should I be worried?
How do I know if my baby's gassy?
Is flash pasteurized juice safe to drink while pregnant? I’ve been drinking it for awhile now, I’m only 5 weeks prego and just realized the bottle says “flash pasteurized”

I’m going to Thailand in 2 weeks. I will be 8 weeks then. Anything I should be careful with?
Has anyone had both Celiacs Disease and Gestational Diabetes?
I will be travelling to bulgaria and im 6 weeks pregnant, worrying about the food there has anyone been there? And also I checked with my gp and told me just to relax and avoid ski
Is it ok to have coconut icecream once in while?
I ate cold fried rice because I forgot to heat it. I’m still in early pregnancy learning everything. It was bought today. Is my baby going to get hurt?!
Is store bought cold smoked salmon safe to eat during pregnancy?
Can I eat snapper?
What’s everyone’s opinion on canned soup while pregnant?
Is it safe to drink diet ginger ale for nausea in first trimester?
Is it safe to eat natto during pregnancy ?
Is it safe to kickbox?
Psyllium husk?
I'm 10 weeks pregnant and I just read that tuna is an absolute "no-no".  I've ate tuna everyday for the past 3 weeks. Will this affect my baby?
Are some types of sushi safe?
Can I drink Sheetz coffee while pregnant?
I am literally paranoid about toxoplasmosis and listeriosis! How high is the risk getting this infections really?
Early pregnancy bloating?
My first trimester.. what kind of foods / things do I need to avoid? & what should I consume most of?
Balsamic vinegar safe?
I am 9 weeks pregnant and I can’t keep anything down. I’ve tried even just eating like soup and ramen to just have something light on my stomach. Any suggestions?
What were your weirdest food cravings?
Is Emergen-c safe to take while pregnant?
Is eating store boughtFrench onion dip made with mayo and sour cream okay? I ate half a container with crackers yesterday without thinking and had vomiting and the runs last night.
I just ate sauerkraut with caraway, and I am worried because I just read that caraway can cause miscarriage...:( am I gonna be ok?!?!?
Why would legs swell during week 25 of pregnancy ?
Is peppermint tea safe?
Recently found out I'm 8 weeks. I used an herbal detox drink about a week prior to knowing. Could I have harmed baby? No ultrasound or blood until 11 weeks I'm just worried.
Fish eggs?
this is my first pregnancy and im scared im doing it wrong i dont think im eating the right foods or eating enough food. what are some good foods to eat while being pregnant?
Is water with Splenda okay to drink?
Can we have small amounts of Indian long pepper
I don’t have a doctor yet, so who do I call for possible food poisoning?
Can you help me please, I have a bit of a problem with food?
Can I eat food out a can after it's been cooked while pregnant?
What can't I eat during my pregnancy?
Raw meat?!
4 weeks pregnant - Diet Coke?
Sunny side up eggs?
Black garlic supplements
Anyone else have trouble with a sore stomach after eating something they usually ate before pregnant? Bread!
Im 23 weeks pregnant and was wondering if it's safe to consume grapefruit? I've heard they can counteract with medicine, all im taking is prenatals and calcium at the moment
Can I eat baleadas sencilla?
Can I eat kiwi fruit in a moderate amount like one per day? Is it safe to eat!!
no appetite at 6 weeks?
Anyone else unable to eat gluten or dairy?
Is it safe to drink red raspberry leaf at 30 weeks?
I cooked roast with meat diaper on it for 2 hours, is it safe for baby to eat it?
I cooked roast with meat diaper on it for 2 hours, is it safe for baby to eat it?
Sea island tartar sauce?  I ate fried fish with sea island tartar sauce and seriously felt like I could die after a few hours I was throwing up EVERYTHING I ate, was it the tartar?
My husband and I have been trying to get pregnant for almost 2yrs; after going vegan, we conceived 6wks later. I'd like to stick with veganism, but is it safe? Things to consider?
I just developed a strange skin rash after vomiting from acid reflux? Before I had vomited, the skin near my right eye had stung a bit but then after, it turned red and inflamed.
What foods to eat during each week of the pregnancy to help development?
Hello, I had a miscarriage last year and now I’m 5 weeks late on my period. I been feeling nauseated and tired lately. Could I be pregnant?
Hey ladies! My family had Thanksgiving early and I had stuffing with Turkey from Bodacious and Cranberry Sauce. Are all three of those things safe? I heated the turkey and Stuffing
Arlo James or Luca James: Which one do you like better for our baby boy and why? Please help!!!! lol
Is kaukauna sharp cheddar spreadable cheese safe to eat
Help!?

Is chamomile tea good for pregnancy?
Can I eat raw vegetables?
Chicken with red spot after frying
What food aversion did you have during pregnancy?
Weird “cravings”?

Is caffeine free chai/roobios tea safe?
Is bone marrow safe to eat during the first trimester?
Can you get too much folic acid?
I ate canned soup for dinner and see it has BPA which is bad. Should I be worried?
I don't like eggs now?
Are ground cherries safe to consume during pregnancy?
How safe is coffee while pregnant? I'm 20 weeks today and avoided caffeine almost completely until now. Im limiting myself to a couple cups in the morning with creamer.
What are safe pregnant women can eat while being a Diabetic?
Fries eggs with runny yolk okay?
I read that products with star anise, like chai tea, can cause a miscarriage. Is this true?
I'm not getting enough protein from my diet. How can I supplement or increase the amount I need without having to eat a great deal more since I have no appetite?
Does the baby get hungry in the womb?
Hello! Please give me advice. I am taking 800mcg Folic Acid and Mercury Free Fish Oil from Whole foods. I won’t see my OB until my 8 weeks. It’s my 1st month today. Am I okay?
Is eating uncooked rice harmful to unborn baby?
generic prenatal?


What can I eat or drink  that will give me more energy?
Fatigue After Meals?
Is ikea ligionberry jam pasturized?
pains? or upset stomach?
Aside from prenatals are there any other vitamins I should be taking?
Fruit leather safe?
can i eat medium rare steak？im at the last day of the third month
Can I break an Omega 3 capsule and drink its contents?
Help ! Caffeine withdrawals or is it something more serious ?
Prenatals causing nausea and migraines?
Is it safe to consume whole golden flaxseed
Can I eat calamari, ranch dressing, hot dogs/corn dogs, pickles, fried rice from hibachi, my normal foods? What should I NOT eat? Please help me.
What is 'normal pregnancy weight gain?
I’m 9 weeks and I’m having a allergic reaction from apples or Carmel idk which one is this common ive never experienced nothing like this?
Is it safe to cook on a gas bbq while pregnant?
Can I eat chilli doritos?
I'm a big foodie and love exotic dishes with different components. Is there an app or book for a foodie's guide to pregnancy? I feel like all I do is google food items.
I'm 11 w 4 d, and food is making me sick, and my grandparents aren't really helping, what do I do?
Has anyone accidentally ate undercooked pork?
Anyone else getting conflicting advice on drinking?
I am 5 weeks and a few days ago I had heavy cramping on one side of my uterus. After a few days it stopped, so I've kinda not worried about it. is it normal?
I’m 9wks and I actually haven’t been constipated but the last few days have had diarrhea. I guess will call OB tomorrow but wondering if this is normal?
Can pregnant women eat beer cheese?
Is it ok to eat from a restaurant buffe? I am 5 weeks pregnant
How to get over food poisoning?
I'm 7 weeks pregnant and ate a spicy tuna sushi roll and California sushi roll... no cramps no vomiting, I was just wondering if I was harming my baby or is everything okay?
Cravings for "your baby is the size of a.." fruit
Right now I'm ten weeks and two days. The start of my pregnancy I couldn't stop eating. Now, I have little desire to eat or drink anything. Is this normal?
almost ate a bad grape?
Hey guys I was hoping someone could give me a good recommendation for a milk replacement during pregnancy? I’m breaking out horribly and get super nauseous after eating dairy
Hi, is it ok to have steamboat when you are pregnant? Is it best to avoid drinking the soup base since all raw food are dumped into it to cook?
Always exhausted after I eat, like no energy and need to sleep. Anyone else?
I dont know what’s healthy eating, my school do not have health foods besides salad, what else could I eat?
Can u eat subs?
What is the best foods to eat to prevent birth defects?
I have the worse loss of appetite since I found out I was pregnant. I entering week 13 tomorrow and I never know what I want to eat. Any suggestions or recipe ideas?
 I'm afraid I'm not drinking enough water?
Isagenix shakes while pregnant. Yes or no?
Is my fetus able to taste what I'm eating?
Ate rare Filet mignon without thinking, should I be worried?
I'm roughly 5 weeks pregnant and every time I eat a certain food I get the worst stomach pain or cramp, why is this and should I avoid this food?
What to eat?
How do I stop hating food during the first trimester? I can have food twice and then just the thought of it makes me wanna run to the bathroom.
is it safe to consume grapes? I have been eating them a lot/craving them. Im 7 wks
Is Yogi tea ok?
Is home made burrito bowl good during pregnancy?
Is Oolong tea drinkable during pregnancy?
Sardines during pregnacy?
Diet coke?
Any recommendations for making baby active at 20 week scan?
Something to help with sickness and nausea?
What kind of fruits can I have ?
Is the PEscience vegan range safe to consume while pregnant?
Fiber rich food?
Are there any spices I should stay away from?
first time mommy. meatss ??
I am in 1st trimester and have diarreha daily (3 days in row) think it's the prenatal vitamins. Can I drink sports drinks (Powerade) to help prevent dehydration?
Pregnancy and gastric sleeve, anyone else going through this?
I've just gone 17 weeks, and I don't feel hungry at all. Then when I try to eat something, I feel sick. Should I be worried?
Struggling maintaining weight?
What vitamin or herbal supplement can I take for mood swings?
Is Halo Top ice cream safe to eat during pregnancy?
What do you think about using splenda as a sweetener?
Is soy safe to eat while pregnant?
I'm a couple days shy of 5 weeks and I started to feel cramping. Nothing severe but it kind of scared me, I also ate hot Cheetos earlier is that normal?
Can you use a used medela pump instyle?
Are there any alternatives for the glucose drink? Are doctors open to them?
Im at 7 weeks, and I have not found much to eat that sounds good except for Pho which might sound odd but is Beef pho in particular a good and nutritional thing to be eating?
Is it safe to eat almond milk yogurt?
Oven baked cheesecake?
Is it okay that I swallowed a cherry pit by accident? I am 18.5 weeks
What prenatal vitamins do u all take? I'm looking into Non-Synthetic (real food) options, but these don't have calcium or DHA. Do u take a separate pill? What brands do you like?
I am 5 weeks pregnant and I drink Saffron Milk daily at night (3 strands in a cup of milk). Is that okay?
This is my first pregnancy, what foods should I stay away from? And what foods should I introduce to my diet?
Fix for extreme heartburn?
I normally drink a lot of coffee. Is caffeine dangerous for my baby?
Is flaxseed safe to consume while pregnant?
Is anyone else grossly full after eating at 6 weeks?
I'm about 6 weeks pregnant and can't eat without getting acid reflux. Is this normal? And is there anything I can take to help?
Is protein powder or some type of protein bar safe for pregnancy?
Sick when I eat anything at 15 weeks? Help!
Needing more salt thank usual?
Can I eat Rhubarb crumble?
Trying to be healthy with pregnancy symptoms please help?
I had a few spoonfuls of a homemade pasta salad I made a week ago, before I thought about the fact it had been in the fridge that long. No mayo. Now freaking out about listeria!?
I'm 7 mnths pregnant & was forced to eat outside maybe once a week for the past 5 mnths. Shd I avoid eating out for the rest of my pregnancy? Have I affected the health of baby
If early pregnant can you still take Blackmores Conception tablets. Have ptetty much a whole box left and dont want to waste money?
Is nitrate bad for the baby?
Hey guys, should I be worried?  I've just consumed large portion of chicken Livers. I'm 4 weeks pregnant
What can I do to have a healthy first trimester?
Im having my 2nd kid after having my 1st 5 years ago When I was pregnant w/ her I weighed about 115 lbs and never lost the baby weight how can I manage my weight w/o effecting bby?
I suffer from tiredness and horrible rotten like taste in my mouth and nasty after taste. As a result I have aversions for a lot of foods. What can I do? I'm 9 weeks along.
Possible raw poultry contamination?
Safe to drink soft drink?
Hi! Does anybody know if an organic tea to help relieve constipation safe to drink while pregnant?
Can I eat cheese?
Is it safe to drink from disposable water bottles while pregnant?
Hello all, I am 5 weeks pregnant and my doctor recommended a combination of vitamins. is it safe to take them all?
I ate a blue cheese salad. Is my baby ok?
I only crave salmon and I can eat a lot in a week is this safe ? This is raw salmon
Is it okay to take b12? Aside from prenatal. I heard b12 helps with energy & i could use a dose
I asked for decaf coffee but got jittery after drinking it. How concerned should I be about accidental caffeine over-consumption?
Is Almond Milk okay? I've been craving it like crazy and no one has answered me! I want the dark chocolate almond milk or the vanilla almond milk.
Is soft served ice cream, like a Wendy's Frosty okay to eat?
I'm 8 wks 2 days & extremely hungry right before bed although eating enough during day I try to satisfy the hunger with saltines or applesauce but nothing seems to satisfy. Advice?
DELI MEAT?!?!
Is it possible to get listeria from Gorgonzola cheese if it's been pasturized?
8 weeks and 5 days pregnant. I have avoided coffee, don't care for it much and alcohol since I am allergic to wine. Can I drink thai ice tea?
I accidentally swallowed a cherry seed and I'm 6 weeks pregnant should I be worried?
Food? Skincare?
What can happen to my baby now that I have gestational diabetes?
Can I have Cup a Soup with a cough and UTI at the same time?
Tea and coffee?
I had a runny egg and oatmeal these past couple mornings. I am now scared I may have hurt my baby...?
Can I eat pho soup while pregnant?
What should I be eating and doing now that I have gestational diabetes?
Can prenatal vitamins be store in the fridge to keep them drugs?
Will eating spicy food make me go into early labor?
Accidentally ate some tomato pate and now concerned about listeria. Anyone know about the risks?
I just found out that I'm pregnant (7weeks) and I was drinking a lot of coffee before I found out. Is that okay? (I've quit since I found out)
I'm 6 weeks along. I'm trying to cook more at home and not give in to my fast food cravings as much. However every time I cook I get super nauseous and don't want dinner. Advice?
Are artichoke hearts safe to eat during pregnancy? And would they need to be cooked before eating?  I love them, but can't find a clear answer.
Food to eat ?
Is sushi ok to eat at 13 weeks?
Is whole milk okay to drink? Or, is low fat really better? There's a lot of debate...
Small cup of coffee every few days, 2nd trimester?
I'm 20 weeks and have been warned to stay away from spicy food. I plan to talk to my ob on my next appt, but I'm wondering in the meantime if you know whether I should avoid spicy?
I am headed to China soon, how can I best avoid food poisoning?
I just realized the mug I've been drinking tea from has mold inside a crevice around the top (just as I was finishing the full mug...). I'm 6 weeks pregnant and concerned!
I was just drinking juice from a glass and by the time i reached the last sip, i saw that there was a crack at the bottom of the glass. Should I be worried? When i felt it, i couldn't feel anything so it was internal
I've read so many different things about what cheeses and snacks I can and any eat. What cheeses am I okay to eat while I'm pregnant with baby?
I'm 24 weeks, and it seems like everytime I lie on my side I want to throw up (I can feel it rising). Is this normal?
Is there a single resource that I can see what I can and cannot eat? I.e. A comprehensive list of all the different seafoods and cheeses.
Can you eat seafood in your second trimester?
I'm 10 weeks pregnant, and I just found out my favorite drink from Starbucks has licorice root in it! (Passion tango lemon iced tea sweetened) should I just throw it out?:(
What fish is safe to eat while pregnant?
Is it safe to drink cranberry juice?
Is it safe to drink cranberry juice?
Eating liquorish 2nd tri????
Is it safe to eat really spicy food during the second and third trimester?
Can I eat lobster tail?
Can eating too much fruit lead to gestational diabetes?
Are farm fresh eggs safe during pregancy?
So I am eight weeks and five days today. I don't eat red meat and I rarely eat chicken. Primarily my protein is fish is crab or shrimp safe I was told it wasn't?
Will spicy chips affect my baby?
Oak Smoked ham is it OK to eat?
what should i pay attention to diet when i am pregnant?
How do I get rid of acid reflux?
During breakfast I ate a cherry tomato and only then noticed a tomato in the same Tupperware had what seemed like a little mold on it. Should I be worried?
I accidentally took Tylenol cold flu instead of the Regular Tylenol !?
Can I drink kombucha?
Can I drink energy drinks when pregnant?
How do I eat healthy with so many food allergies?
Has anyone travelled to Bali while pregnant?
This might sounds crazy or dumb but, should I eat instant soups if I'm pregnant? I might be overreacting but what's your opinion?
Constant nausea relief!?
Can I drink raw milk?
First baby at 19 7weeks need advice ?
Can I go on a diet?
Are aloe vera drinks safe to drink in second trimester?
Mam bottles vs dr brown
Anyone have and extreme sweet tooth during their pregnancy? All I can think about is ice cream and and Chocolate! Trying to watch calorie and sugar intake but hard to resist!
I consumed alcohol on New Years and I'm 11 weeks pregnant is my child ok? I'm really concerned.
Are you allowed to eat clams?
Throwing up, dry heaving, and diarrhea? I need help, any advice will be so appreciated!
Why I have I only gained 3 pounds and I'm already on my 2nd trimester?
Glucosamine Chondroitin?
Is it bad to hold your breath while pregnant?
Is it safe to drink a detoxing tea any time during    pregnancy?
Is it safe to eat hummus?
Too many vitamins... Did I cause major damage?
Can I eat imitation crab meat?
Hey I'm 8 weeks pregnant and ate sushi is my baby ok ? I mean I've been craving for it for weeks now. But only ate a few pieces. Not vomiting or anything or cramps?
I would like to ask is it safe to air travel while i am pregnant
Hey. is it ok to drink fizzy drinks during first trimester.  the nausea is killing me and the fizzy drinks are one thing I can keep down
I don't like to eat anything. I am 9 weeks pregnant. I keep puking and am tired all day.
Is it possible to overdo it when taking vitamins while pregnant?
Is alfredo sauce from a restaurant (Johnny Carino's) safe while pregnant?
Is it safe to eat hollandaise sauce while pregnant?
My breasts are so sore! I have taken evening primrose oil when that has happened when I have been on my period and it totally works. Is it safe to take while pregnant?
My breasts are so sore! I have taken evening primrose oil when that has happened when I have been on my period and it totally works. Is it safe to take while pregnant?
Sugar level dropped during 35 weeks. Suddenly felt dizzy and everything blacked out. Couldn't hear or speak.Mom gave some sugar and then felt better. Will it harm the baby?
Raw honey safe?
What snacks should I pack in my hospital bag?
Can you drink soda while pregnant?
What protein shakes/powders are safe to consume while pregnant?
I throw up milk immediately?
Benefits of pomegranate juice while pregnant? I heard that pomegranate extract causes miscarriage so I want to make sure pomegranate juice is safe to consume
How safe is cooked sushi?
How many of you momma' to be cut out caffeine completely and how many of you just stay within the safe daily amount of 150-200mg? Just curious!
Sleepy time tea
Is Sleepy Time camomile tea ok during pregnancy?
Can you drink hot chocolate?
8 weeks & Crawfish
What protein shake do you guys use?
Is it okay I've been craving pizza I'm 6 weeks
What are the best foods to prevent morning sickness?
Fasting in first trimester
Can I eat soup
Aspartame
Foods to avoid throughout pregnancy?
Is it safe to eat salmon during pregnancy? My father in-law invited us over for dinner but I've decided to avoid parts of the menu to be safe.
Is fish oil, which has been purified to remove mercury, okay to take as a supplement while pregnant? The brand is Nature Made.
Best foods to eat when breast feeding?
Can't eat anything, not hungry, weight loss.
First Trimester weight gain
Can i eat tater sauce? I'm 6 weeks Pregnant and just ate it
Is there a good list of foods to eat or snack on, when you have lost your appetite completely?
I ate Taco Bell and about less than an hour later I vomited once. I'm 15 weeks pregnant and I'm kinda worried something is wrong. Has anyone ever experienced anything like that?
If I cooked chicken can I eat it cold (like in a salad) or do I have to reheat it every time I eat it out of the fridge to kill any bacteria?
Is it safe to use Op con A eye drops regularly (i.e. Once/day) during pregnancy?   My on said it was fine but wanted to check. Thanks.
Is it safe to use Op con A eye drops regularly (i.e. Once/day) during pregnancy?   My on said it was fine but wanted to check. Thanks.
How much daily caffeine is safe?


Sugar Substitutes
Washing plastic Tupperware in dishwasher ?
Is there a list of cheeses that are safe and unsafe?
I'm 10 weeks pregnant and still I've been experiencing all day sickness! 😩 I've been eating ginger chew gummies but I read somewhere ginger tea could help? Anyone recommend?
Does anyone know of any health concerns with deer meat?
Does anyone know if squid ink pasta is okay to eat when pregnant?
Is pregnancy tea ok?
I'm 8 weeks and I have white discharge and I feel like the baby is on my bladder could he or she be bigger than a raspberry?
Is eating around lunch meat in a salad safe?
What types of fish could I eat at 24 weeks pregnant?
Hey! I m 29 weeks pregnant. Everything i eat, i throw out. I have digestion problem. I am taking tabs for vomiting. But nothing is helping. So i m feeling weekness.
Is it safe to drink apple cider while pregnant?
CHEESUS! I am so confused!
Can you have frozen custard
Sick after sugar?
Can I eat lunch meat if I cook it first?
Hi, I'm 6 and a bit weeks pregnant and I've started having food aversions. Do these go away after first trimester?
Eating less since finding out I was pregnant.
Is it bad to drink coffee while pregnant?
Is drinking cold water okay for my baby
I had a chicken salad wrap yesterday for lunch from our local deli. I'm seeing mixed reviews about pre made salads. I had no idea bc I assumed not lunch meat and cooked chicken?
I accidentally had a few bites of tiramisu cake from Whole Foods, any major harm caused?
Can I eat salami while pregnant?
i'm currently 10 weeks pregnant. I had 2 glasses of whole milk with dinner tonight and am very constipated lately. Lets just say I didnt have a probaly w/ that tonight.  Lactose?
Honey Nut Cheerios for 7 month old?
Baby milk on holiday
Went out to dinner , had a bite of a bread pudding with spirited Creme anglaise but didn't know until after , have I harmed the baby ?
Can you eat Tuna?
Aloe during pregnancy
Can we now eat runny eggs when pregnant?
Do I need to heat canned tuna before I eat it?
Im 7 weeks and just ate rare steak? Will the baby be okay?
Why does my baby have white on his tongue
Can pregnant women eat crawfish?
Is lemon water bad for the baby?
Pregnant and diagnosed with food sensitivities. Can avoiding these foods prevent my baby from having the same sensitivities?
Is it frowned upon to have family bring in food after the delivery?? I really want a sandwich right after labor!!
Ate 1/2 a deli sndwich w/o thinking
how much is too much sugar
Is it safe to eat veggies, fruit, store bought hummas while pregnant?
Dannon Light & Fit Greek safe to eat?
Is local raw honey safe in the first trimester?
Coffee alternatives
Ordered an iced coffee, got a cold brew @ 11 weeks pregnant!
Is MSG dangerous to eat during pregnancy?
Help!! I drank aloe juice!!
Is it okay to drink protein shakes while pregnant?
Baby nutrition - what should I be eating?
What should I avoid eating early in pregnancy?
Uncontrollable eating first trimester
Salad dressings
Which ice creams are safest from listeria?
is cornmeal porridge safe in pregnancy
Seafood intake
Small glass of wine with dinner on my birthday?
Im 11 weeks and 5 days and craving a grilled hotdog so bad but is it safe?
What seasonings are good for you and which ones aren't, while pregnant?
Is it safe to drink Kombucha while pregnant?
Baby shower foods
Is it safe to eat pomfret (butterfish) in 13th week?
At what age can my baby start drinking juice?
I am 5w6d i love sushi and seweed salad and i cant stop can i keep eating it ?
Is pepperoni ok?
Has anyone eaten Arby's roast beef when pregnant?
Can you drink honey and lemon tea while pregnant?
I'm craving a Subway sandwich. Is this okay to eat or should I stay away? I keep hearing mixed stories on it being okay or not.
Are Quest bars safe to eat while pregnant?
Is canned coconut milk good during pregnancy?
Are sugar-free drinks okay to drink ?
Burger
Thoughts on shellfish?
Is sesame oil safe to eat while pregnant?
Can I have Arbonne protein shakes?
Are artificial sweeteners safe?
How much baby food should my 7-month-old be eating a day?
Can I give my 8-month-old chamomile tea?
Probiotic Yogurt
first time mommy to be
Is taking Emergen-C while pregnant okay?
Is bubble tea safe during pregnancy?
I ate raw salmon today but only 3 small pieces. Is that okay?
Developing a peanut allergy during pregnancy?
Is it safe to drink coconut juice or green tea in your first trimester?
Can husband eat WIC foods?
What are you all eating straight after birth?
Is it bad to drink cinnamon tea at 38 weeks pregnant?
What are good portion sizes and feeding schedules like for a 9-month-old?
Anybody know if it is safe to drink redbull in moderation?
Coffee?
Can I crush my rainbow prenatal vitamin in apple sauce or yogurt?
What to eat for lunch?
How much tuna can a pregnant woman have?
Is it ok to do a 4 day juice cleanse while 6 weeks pregnant?
Has anyone drank coconut coffee while pregnant?
Am I allowed to eat beef jerky?
Is green tea safe during pregnancy?
Is Chai Tea okay to drink while pregnant?
Stomach Pains
Are sweets okay during the first trimester? What's your go-to?
Is Mayo safe?
At 4-6 months, what should I be feeding my baby?
Can I eat bean sprouts?
Can pregnant women eat spicy foods?
Is it okay to drink soft drinks while pregnant?
Are herbal teas unsafe during pregnancy??
Herbal Bitters before I knew I was pregnant?
Is it okay to eat ramen noodles?
I know food cravings are common, but what about food aversions?
What foods are unsafe for breastfeeding?
Loss of appetite? Any good shakes?
Why can't I eat soft cheese when I'm pregnant?
Third trimester Tea
protein powder
Is it safe to drink tart cherry concentrate mixed with water to help me sleep? I wake up at least 2 a night and usually once is for 30 minutes or more.
How bad is it to still drink soda in the 3rd trimester?
Cooking with cheese &/or alcohol
Chewing Gum
Healthy Snacks.
Is Braggs Apple cider vinegar safe to drink? I've heard mixed reviews. Has anyone taken it and been ok?
Freaking out! Is stash lemon ginger tea ok to drink while pregnant?
What can I feed my 9 month old with no teeth?
Is it safe to eat noodles while pregnant
Is pasteurized blue cheese safe to eat?
When you eat it feels like the food is stuck in your throat
Is protein powder safe during pregnancy?
Is herbal tea ok?
Is it okay to drink coffee while trying to conceive?
Fizzy drinks
Can pregnant women eat cold cuts?
Can I juice at home while pregnant?
Can I eat peanut butter
Can you have Dairylea brand cheese when pregnant?
Help! I'm six weeks, with violent voimitting and diarrhea?
Worst craving for ravioli. Can I?
I ate raw oysters is that gonna effect my baby?
Lasagna